<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ways to Earn Online</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">Make Money Online</string>
    <string name="See">Read Now</string>
    <string name="des">\n\n\n\nWe have described about 32 ways to earn money online</string>
    <string name="help">\nIn this app you can learn about making money online ,we have described a lot of ways for you to
        read and implement .\n\n You can choose your preferred method and read about it then follow it in real life to make money from that method </string>
    <string name="cover_title">Top ways </string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">Read about top 32 ways</string>

    <string name="youtube">
        Starting a Youtube channel is the simplest way of all and needs no investment.
YouTube gets almost 5 billion video views per day which proves its power on the internet.
        <b>Felix Kjellberg</b>, the owner of <b>PewDiePie</b> (a YouTube account), has earned 12 million dollars in 2017 from running a single YouTube channel.
\nYou too can see such success if you capitalize on the opportunity that YouTube provides us currently.
        \n\n\n<u><b>Suitable For :-</b></u>
\n\n\nPeople who love to create videos, like to talk about a video, shoot documentaries or short films.
        \n\n\n<u><b>Skills Required :-</b></u>
\n\n\nAbility to create a video using software tools or record a video using your mobile phone or camcorder.
        \n\n\n<u><b>Time Required For Starting A YouTube Channel :-</b></u>
\n\n\nVirtually you can start within minutes. You will just have to visit YouTube.com, create a channel and upload videos.
\n\n\n<u><b>Tips :-</b></u>
\n\n\n1. Create a YouTube channel around a specific theme such as Humor, Tutorial, Recipe, etc. Don\'t just go out create any random unrelated videos channel.
\n\n\nFor example, if you love gadgets, you can create a gadget reviews channel where you review latest gadgets and help people to decide whether it\'s a right choice for them.
\n\n\n2. Select a theme in which you are really interested. Analyze other videos related to your topic, see how many views those videos get.
\n\n\nIt will help you to get an overview of how many people are interested in your theme.
\n\n\n3. Generally, more the views more beneficial the theme is. As more people are searching for it.
\n\n\n4. Check out if there\'s any concept missing in the currently existing videos related to your theme.
You can cover these concepts in your videos to fetch more views.
\n\n\n5. Give your best to engage with your audience. Study the comments you get on your videos, learn the hidden expectations that your audience has from you.
\n\n\n6. Try to find out what they like about your videos and what they don\'t. Study which videos get the highest retention rate and find the reasons behind them.
\n\n\n7. Spy on your competitors and try to model the things that are working for them. But never try to copy them, always maintain your uniqueness.
\n\n\n8. Always try to improvise each new video from the last one.
So when you look at your first videos after few years, you should think aww how bad I was earlier.
That\'s a good sign; it shows that you\'ve improved.
\n\n\n9. Experiment, experiment, and experiment. Never fear to try something new and see how it works.
Experiments are the only way where you can find new and exciting stuff which can catapult you way ahead of your competitors.
\n\n\n10. Finally, try to collaborate with other YouTuber\'s who are doing similar work.
Learn their strategies and mindset. Working together can do wonders for your channel.
\n\n\n11. Have fun. Do the things that you love and enjoy your life.
        \n\n\n<u><b>How To Monetize :-</b></u>
\n\n\nThe general rule for monetization in YouTube is straightforward. More views your videos get, more money you will earn.
        You will have to enable the monetize option in your YouTube channel settings. It is very simple.

</string>
    <string name="blog">Being a blogger is one of the easiest ways to earn money from home. Unlike any other job,
    if you are blogging from home. You don\’t need to work 9-5.\n
You can work at any time of the day with ease. But beware blogging takes time before it starts making money for you.\n
So I suggest you jump into this field slowly. If you have a day job, don\’t quit it. Start part-time with your blog.\n
Once it is on the stage where it is earning you more than your comfortable limits, then it\’s
    the best time to turn into full-time blogging mode.
    \n\n\n<u><b>Suitable For :-</b></u>
\n\n\nPeople who love to write and would like to share their knowledge and expertise with the world.
    \n\n\n<u><b>Skills Required :-</b> </u>
\n\n\nAbility to express knowledge in writing with simpler yet efficient way.
    \n\n\n<u><b>Time Required For Starting A Blog :-</b></u>
\n\n\nThe time required depends upon your level of expertise if you are an expert you
    can easily start a blog within few hours. For a complete beginner, a day or two would be sufficient.
    \n\n\n<u><b>Tips :-</b></u>
\n\n\n1. Start a blog about something in which you are really good at.
For example, if you love traveling and you have visited a lot of places then start a travel blog.
\n\n\n2. Always try to limit your blog to a particular domain. Don\’t put content on multiple domains in one blog.
For example, writing about recipe tips on a fashion blog. Keep your blog specific to one domain only.
\n\n\n3. Using your experience and expertise try to create a unique and phenomenal content.
    Try to give a lot of value to your readers. Write about something that will make a difference in your reader\'s life.
\n\n\n4. Listen to the readers of your blog. Try to solve the problems they are facing.
    Always reply to their comments. Make them feel better.
\n\n\n5. Be committed to your blog. A blog is like a relationship. Give it some love,
    and it will flourish. Ignore it, and it will die a death. There\’s no point in being
    half-hearted in your blogging efforts - if you don\’t care about it, why should anyone else?
\n\n\n6. Think about content, style, the tone of voice, audience, etc. Look at the people
    who are already doing what you\’re planning to do.
    \n\n\n<u><b>Ask yourself the following questions: </b></u>
\n\n\n•	How will I stand out from the crowd?
\n\n\n•	What can I say that hasn\’t already been said?
\n\n\n•	What\’s my unique selling point?
\n\n\n•	Why do I want to do this?
\n\n\n7. Be professional in the way you handle and grow your blog. Don\’t criticize other brands,
    bloggers or people. Remember what goes around comes around. You don\’t want something you\’ve
    said to come back and bite you one day.
\n\n\n8. Be open-minded and willing to collaborate with other creatives. You\’ll meet some fantastic
    and awe-inspiring people.
    \n\n\n<u><b>How To Monetize :-</b></u>
\n\n\nYou can monetize your blog by recommending products or services related to your blog\'s
    topic either by writing an informative article or placing banner ads on your blog\’s relevant pages.
You can earn handsome commissions when a person buys a product recommended by you.
Another way is you can place Google Adsense ads on your blog. More people click on your ads more money you will make.
</string>
    <string name="monetize"><u><b>What is Affiliate Marketing?</b></u>
\n\n\n\nAffiliate marketing is a type of performance-based marketing in which a business rewards a certain
        percentage of commission for each product bought by the customers who are brought
        by the affiliate\'s own marketing efforts.

        \n\n\n<u><b>Suitable For :-</b></u>
\n\n\nPeople who love to talk, write, explain and have the ability to persuade.
\n\n\n<u><b>Skills Required :-</b></u>
\n\n\nAbility to promote a product online using social media, videos, ads, etc.
\n\n\n<u><b>Time Required For Starting Affiliate Marketing :-</b></u>
\n\n\nVirtually within an hour. You just need to select an online product that pays a commission
        when you promote and sell it using your affiliate link.
\n\n\n<u><b>Tips :-</b></u>
\n\n\n1. Select an online product from the domain in which you are well conversant with.
        For example, if you are a dietician then select a product related to diet.
There are lots of products available in every domain you just need to focus on which domain is suitable for you.
\n\n\n2. Places to find products: Clickbank.com, Shareasale.com, Jvzoo.com. These websites have thousands
        of products listed from multiple domains.
\n\n\n3. Choose a product that pays you at least 50% commission on each sale.
\n\n\n4. Most product websites handle affiliate link generation and payouts so you don’t need to worry about how
        you\’ll get your commissions.
Just get your custom affiliate link created by the vendor and start promoting it.
\n\n\n5. If you want to earn instant money from affiliate marketing try to promote
        your affiliate link on social sites such as Facebook, Twitter, Digg, StumbleUpon, and Reddit.
        \n\n\n<u><b>How To Monetize :-</b></u>
\n\n\nMonetization is simple, just make more people buy the product through your affiliate link.
        Create a Facebook page or Banner ads about the product.
Tell people how the product will help them to solve their problems.
Improve people\’s knowledge about the domain and help them to solve other related problems.

</string>
    <string name="niche">\n\n\n<u><b>What is a Niche Website?</b></u>
\n\n\n\nA Niche Website is a small website focused on one particular topic which shares all the information
        relevant to the topic that is both useful and interesting for the target audience.
A niche website can be of few pages or even of hundreds of pages depending upon the size of the niche.
        \n\n\n<u><b>Suitable For :-</b></u>
\n\n\n1. People who have an interest in a very specific topic within a large domain.
For example, in large a domain like Yoga, you can choose specific sub-domain such as \‘Yoga to lose weight.\’
\n\n\n2. People who love to talk, write, explain and have the ability to persuade.
        \n\n\n<u><b>Skills Required :-</b></u>
\n\n\n1. Ability to create Niche website based on specific sub-domain using Wordpress, Blogger or other available software and tools.
\n\n\n2. Ability to promote the website using social media, ads etc.
        \n\n\n<u><b>Time Required For Starting A Niche Website :-</b></u>
\n\n\nYou can start a Niche Website within a day. But creating a good content for the website might take time.
        \n\n\n<u><b>Tips :-</b></u>
\n\n\n1. Write out as many niche site ideas as you can, using the sub-domain that interests you the most.
\n\n\n2. Narrow down your niche idea based on finding the answers to the following questions:
\n\n\n•	What is the audience size of your niche?
\n\n\n•	Is your audience known for spending money on purchasing the niche related products?
\n\n\n•	Are there multiple products available which you review on your site?
\n\n\n•	Are there affiliate programs that provide more than 50% commissions?
\n\n\n•	What is your investment budget?
\n\n\n3. Create at least 10 articles of rich content with 1000 words that will provide value to your niche targeted audience.
\n\n\n4. Sign up for at least 2 affiliate programs that offer products related to your niche with more than 50% commissions.
\n\n\n5. Do keyword research and find at least 15-20 niche relevant search terms and try to rank your site for them.
\n\n\n6. Try to network with the owners of the authority blogs in your niche and find guest blogging opportunities.
        \n\n\n<u><b>How To Monetize :-</b> </u>
\n\n\nPromote the products relevant to the topic of your niche website by placing affiliate
        links in the content and sidebar of your site.
Try to get more visitors to your site by doing SEO,
        forum marketing, social media and paid ads. More people visit your niche site and buy products through your affiliate link, more money you make.
How about creating 10 more Niche Websites with every site generating
        $500 a month in affiliate commission that would be $5000 of passive income per month.
</string>
    <string name="kindle">
        Publishing a Kindle eBook is another simple way of generating consistent passive income.
Did you know that Amazon.com is the biggest competitor to Google than any other search engine like Yahoo or Bing?
More shoppers try to search for a product on Amazon than on any traditional search engine.
When people want in-depth information on a specific topic, they don\’t search for blog posts on Google but instead,
        try to find a highly recommended book on Amazon.
Your aim should be to leverage the power of Amazon.com\’s growing outreach and popularity to 
        generate a stable passive income source.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For :-</u></b> 
\n\n\nPeople who have in-depth knowledge of a certain topic or love to do research and explain it in an easily understood from.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required :-</u></b> 
\n\n\n1. Ability to provide detailed insights on a particular topic. 
\n\n\n2. Ability to provide some extraordinary tips for solving people\’s problems.
\n\n\nTime Required For Creating An eBook -
\n\n\nThe time required completely depends on the creator of the eBook. What topics he or she wants to cover? 
        How many details does the creator want to include?
\n\n\nThese are the important factors that define the time required.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Research, research, and research. It is the key to successful Kindle eBook product. 
        Research about what people are looking for in the domain related to your eBook\'s topic.
For example, if you are creating an eBook on \‘Yoga to lose weight\' 
        look for how many people are looking for yoga exercises to lose weight on 
        the internet and Amazon? What are their expectations from a book? 
You can easily conduct this research by studying the comments, 
        reviews, and popularity of the existing competitor\'s books on Amazon.
\n\n\n2. Write for one reader. When you know your ideal reader, you know how much he/she already knows. 
        You can avoid boring him/her with obvious information, 
        and you can provide exactly the information he/she\’s looking for. 
\n\n\n3. Check out how many people are asking questions on the topic you have chosen, 
        using websites such as Quora, Yahoo Answers, and WikiAnswers. 
        More questions mean more people are looking for answers and that\’s a good sign.  
\n\n\n4. Look out for the market gaps in your selected domain. And see whether there\’s demand for some topic, 
        see whether your eBook can cater that demand. 
\n\n\n5. Visit Amazon.com and see how many books are present on your selected domain. 
        Are people buying those books? This will help you to understand 
        the demand and purchasing ability of the market in your domain.
\n\n\n6. Find a few friendly readers who match your ideal 
        reader profile and give them your first draft. Not only will they 
        help make your book better, it will also boost your confidence.  
\n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\nSign up to Kindle Direct Publishing Program, with this you award 
        exclusive distribution rights for your Kindle eBook to Amazon.
This will allow you to sell your eBook in all the countries where 
        Amazon.com is available giving it a massive exposure at launch.
Create a small niche site on the related topic and promote 
        your eBook through it. The more eBooks you sell the more money you make.
</string>
    <string name="membershipsite">\n\n\n<b><u>What is a Membership Site?</u></b>
\n\n\nA membership site is a private website, with exclusive content available only to the signed up members.
It usually provides members with the ability to interact with each other. They pay a monthly fee for being a member of the website.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
\n\n\nPeople who like to interact with, guide and lead a community.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. In-depth knowledge of any particular domain.
\n\n\n2. Ability to research new things and constantly generate new and helpful content.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Creating A Membership site -</u></b>
\n\n\nDepends on the domain expertise of the creator.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. In the beginning, keep the fee for joining the membership site ridiculously low.
        Aim to create a minimum viable product instead of creating a perfect product.
        You can always improve your site in later stages.
\n\n\n2. If you\’ve never been a part of any membership site till now,
        consider joining a few related to your domain. Study those sites.
\n\n\n3. Find what\’s working well for you and other members of that site?
        What\’s makes it worth the monthly fee and how could you replicate this?
\n\n\n4. Interact and engage with members. Your membership site shouldn\’t
        be the one that only drip feeds the content, with little or no input from the owner.
You must provide insider access for your members who want to communicate with you. Even if you\’re busy,
        you must spend at least half an hour a day to get involved with your membership site.
You can do this by many ways, such as you can interact with the members answer their
        questions or even lead an interaction inside the forum.
\n\n\n5. Run group events and challenges to increase members\’ engagement with your site.
        Organize regular events, challenges, or similar.
Make it easy for members to participate. Offer prizes, display leaderboards or
        similar such things creates a great incentive for members to participate and get involved.
\n\n\n6. Periodically review what\’s working and what isn\’t. Try to adapt the site based on the member\'s needs.
For example, if you offer most of your content in text format but your members are
        engaging more with the video content then shift from text-based to video content.
\n\n\n7. Try to introduce new initiatives and see how your audience is responding to it. Such as live Q&amp;A calls or similar.
But be careful, don\’t overwhelm members with several different initiatives at once. Introduce one thing at a time.
        \n\n\n<b><u>How to Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\nMonetization is very simple. More members sign up to your website more income you generate from the monthly fees that members pay.
</string>
    <string name="flipa">

       \n\n\n<b><u>What is Flippa.com?</u></b>

   \n\n\n Flippa.com is an online marketplace for selling and buying websites.

    \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For - </u></b>

    \n\n\nPeople who like to develop websites.
   \n\n\n<b><u> Skills Required -</u></b>
    \n\n\nIn-depth knowledge of Wordpress platform and website creation.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Creating A Website -</u></b>
    \n\n\nDepends on the expertise of the developer in website creation.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Choose a topic you are passionate about. You need to be passionate about the subject your website focuses on.
       If you launch a website about something that you don\'t care about, you will lose
       interest very quickly and inevitably stop working on it.
    \n\n\n2. Think about your long-term business model. To make your website successful you should do a lot of research beforehand.
    \n\n\nTry to find the answers to the following questions:\n\n\n• Who are your direct competitors?
    \n\n\n•	How do your competitors make money?
    \n\n\n•	How will your website make money?
   \n\n\n •	How can you make your website stand out from others?
    \n\n\n•	How long will it take to monetize your website?
    \n\n\n3. Choose a domain name that is relevant to your topic and appeals to your target audience.
    \n\n\nA good domain name is an essential part of branding your blog. Choose a .COM
       as your domain extension because it looks more professional.
    \n\n\n4. Choose a reliable paid host like Hostgator, Bluehost or anyone that might suit your needs.
    \n\n\n5. You need to make your website\'s design and layout look very professional.
       Believe it or not but first-time visitors will make a judgment about your blog within
       first 10 seconds of loading, so you need to make sure that your website\’s design appeals to them and they like it.
       \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Sign up and register your website on Flippa.com. Flippa works on bidding model,
       the highest bidder gets the ownership of the website.
    \n\n\n2. Set the bid price of your website 10 times greater than the current monthly income of your site.
       For example, if your site is earning $500 per month then you can set the basic selling bid price of your site
       to at least $5000.
    \n\n\n3. Start the auction and wait for bids. People will start bidding for
       purchasing your site. Once you receive the bid that satisfies your target selling price,
       then finalize the deal with the bidder.
    \n\n\n4. Flippa will manage all the payment and other technical stuff for
       you and you\'ll receive your commissions via your selected payment method.
    </string>
    <string name="udemy">\n\n\n<b><u>What is Udemy.com?</u></b>
\n\n\nUdemy.com is an online learning marketplace. Udemy has a huge list of courses in everything from
        programming to yoga to photography and much more.
\n\n\nYou can create a course in the text, audio, and video formats.
        Every course is available on demand and students can learn at their own pace, on their own time and on any device.
\n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For - </u></b>
\n\n\nPeople who like to teach, explain and solve problems.
\n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required - </u></b>
\n\n\n1. In-depth knowledge of any domain of your choice.
\n\n\n2. Ability to express knowledge in easily understood form.
\n\n\n3. Ability to create and record high-quality videos.
\n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Creating A Video Course -</u></b>
\n\n\nDepends on the scope of the course, the number of modules included and time required for preparation.
\n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Pick a topic in which you are specialized in. Study the courses relevant to your topic
        and see how many people are interested and have actually enrolled in the courses.
\n\n\n2. This will give you a rough understanding of the people who are interested
        in your topic and willing to invest in your course.
\n\n\n3. Study the other available courses and find out the things which
        you can offer that will make your course much better, different than other available courses.
\n\n\n4. Identify your audience level and then create the course content.
For example, you need to first decide whether your course is for beginner level or expert level audience.
Then accordingly you need to create your course content which appeals to the right audience.
\n\n\n5. Make sure your course title and description are optimized for appealing your target
        audience. Try to answer the frequent questions that your audience asks in your course description.
\n\n\n6. Deliver at least 80% of your course in video format as it is the most engaging way of interaction. Also, keep the length of each video lesson between 2-10 minutes.
\n\n\n7. Build a rapport with the audience, and engage.
        You can always do quiz ups between lectures to make it engrossing and interactive.
        \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Udemy gets a lot of daily visitors so there is a good chance that your course will get
        noticed and people will enroll in and you will start earning money.
\n\n\n2. You can even start a small blog on your course-related topics and promote your course.
\n\n\n3. More people sign up for your course more money you make.
</string>
    <string name="fiver">\n\n\n<b><u>What is Fiverr.com?</u></b>
\n\n\nFiverr.com is a global online marketplace which offers tasks, services, and products, starting at a cost of $5.
\n\n\nFiverr gets almost 4.7 million visits per month. Your aim should be to leverage Fiverr\’s powerful
        visitor base to reach more people and sell your services or products to them.
\n\n\nEvery service or task you offer on Fiverr is called a GIG. With Fiverr\’s
        millions of visitor base, you don\’t need much to worry about your gig\’s
        promotion and payment handling as Fiverr handles this for you.
\n\n\nAll you need to do is focus on delivering high-quality work
        to maintain your ratings, as ratings given by your customers will have a
        huge impact on the failure or success of your gig.
\n\n\nPeople offer a diverse variety of services on
        Fiverr which ranges from Graphics and Design, Digital Marketing,
        Music and Audio, Advertising to anything you can practically think of.
\n\n\nRemember you can sell your gig at any price, $5 is just the minimum price.
\n\n\nTop Fiverr gig sellers make over $50,000 a year by leveraging the platform and providing high-quality services.
        n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. People who love to help others by making their easier.

\n\n\n2. People who love the freedom to work, doing what they really like.
        n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
\n\n\nPeople having in-depth skills in any particular area, using which they can help other people
        to complete their tasks or ease their life.
        n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Creating A Gig On Fiverr -</u></b>
\n\n\nYou can create a Gig on Fiverr almost within an hour. All you need to do is first sign up on Fiverr.
While creating a gig you\’ll have to insert your gig\’s title, upload gig\’s image, write gig description
        and insert relevant tags and keywords.
        n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Find your best skills - The first thing you need to do is sit down quietly and figure out the
        skills of which you are the strongest and stick to tasks related to them till you see some success.
For e.g. if you are a person who can design logos and websites,
        then you should create and sell those gigs in Fiverr that are focused on logo creation and web designing.
\n\n\n2. Do your initial homework - Before diving into gig
        creation you must do some research to ensure that the gig you are
        planning to offer has interested buyers. What if you have a wonderful gig idea, but it didn\'t
        sell? To avoid such situation you must undertake necessary research
        to understand what buyers in your niche are looking for.
\n\n\n3. Find popular gigs related to your skill set - One of the best ways of seeing success
        with Fiverr is to dig out the popular gigs related to your skill set, study them, then model your gig accordingly.
\n\n\nMost important metrics you should look at while studying other gigs are its:
\n•	Title
\n•	Description
\n•	Image
\n•	Pricing  strategy
\n•	Upsell strategy
\n•	Bonus strategy
\n\n\n4. Craft your gig\’s title - Now as you are ready with all the research data, jump into gig creation.
        Obviously, here title creation will be your first step. Following are the steps you must follow to
        optimize your gig\’s title.
\n\n\n-  Based on your research data model your gig title, use intriguing words into the title to ensure it
        catches your target customers the attention and is relevant to him/her.
\n\n\nFor example, if you are offering a logo designing gig. You should consider using titles such as
\n\n\n> I\’ll design 3 MAGNIFICENT logos in 24 hours
\n\n\n> I\’ll design a PROFESSIONAL logos with free revisions
\n\n\n> I\’ll design 2 STUNNING logos BONUS Free editable file
\n\n\n- All the above titles are beautifully crafted because they include two important things.
\n\n\nFirst, they all have intriguing words such as MAGNIFICIENT, PROFESSIONAL, STUNNING and BONUS. These words
        definitely help to catch the attention of the right people.
\n\n\nSecondly, they all are appealing to the most important aspects that any person who wants to design a logo is looking at.
\n\n\nFor example, the first title \“3 MAGNIFICENT logos in 24 hours\”
        will appeal to the people who are in urgent need of a logo.
\n\n\nThe second title \“PROFESSIONAL logos with free revisions\”
        will appeal to the kind of people who want the option of incorporating their changes into logo design.
\n\n\nThe third title \“2 STUNNING logos BONUS Free editable file\” will appeal to the people
        who have some knowledge of logo designing and want to customize the logo on their own.
\n\n\n5. Create your gig\’s image - While doing initial homework
        you must have observed that some gigs have better images than
        other which makes them really stand out. Shortlist such images and take inspiration from them while modeling your image.
Once you\’re ready with the initial idea use free
        online image editing tools such as Pixlr or BeFunky to create your gig\’s image.
\n\n\n6. Write gig\’s description - Your gig\’s description plays an important role in
        convincing your potential customers to place an order with you. So you must ensure that your gig\'s
        description is precise, clear and appealing to your potential customers.
Study other top related gig\’s descriptions to get some inspiration and model your description on them.
Remember, don\’t ever copy other gig\’s description it will get you banned.
        Just use theirs to get ideas to create your unique description.
Also, make sure you\’re listing your gig into the right category to maintain its relevance.
\n\n\n7. Use right tags - Tags play the most important role in ranking your gig higher. Most of the people don\’t
        realize its importance, so it provides you with the best opportunity to overtake them
        if you optimize your gig properly using accurate tags.
\n\n\n8. Apart from all the points mentioned above, you need to make sure that your
        work is credible and unique on Fiverr. There might be many logo designers out there on
        Fiverr, but if you are the one who understands the needs of your clients and delivers the work in
        the best possible way then you\’ll be able to secure them as your client for a long time.
        \n\n\n<b><u>How to Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\nMonetization is very simple. More people place orders with you more money you make.
\n\n\nYour delivery work influences your user ratings which directly affects your order placement.
\n\n\nThe simple rule of thumb is, higher the user ratings, higher your orders will be.
\n\n\nFiverr handles all your transactions securely so you don\’t need to worry about any payment processing issues.
</string>
    <string name="ebay">\n\n\n<b><u>What is eBay?</u></b>
\n\n\neBay.com is the most popular website to buy and sell goods on the internet. It\’s a place where individuals and businesses can buy or sell new or second-hand items, from books and clothes to cars to almost anything.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Here\'s how eBay works:</u></b>
\n\n\n1.	A seller lists an item on eBay, almost anything from antiques to mobile phones, books to sporting goods.
\n\n\n2.	The seller chooses whether to sell the item at a fixed price or accept only bids (auction-type listing).
\n\n\n3.	In an auction-type listing, the bidding opens at a price the seller specifies and remains on eBay for a certain number of days.
\n\n\n4.	Buyers then place bids on the item. When the listing ends, the buyer with the highest bid wins.
\n\n\n5.	In a fixed price listing, the first buyer willing to pay the seller\'s price gets the item.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
\n\n\nPeople who are self-motivated and know how to spread the word – to friends, family members, acquaintances and strangers using online or offline mediums.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
\n\n\nSome experience of selling goods online or offline is welcome, along with a business savvy mind.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Time Required To Start Selling On eBay -</u></b>
\n\n\nTo start selling you first need to create an eBay account and a PayPal account. After that, you need to enlist your product for which you\’ll need some product pictures and write an appealing description.
Even if you are a beginner you can all the above tasks within a day or two.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. If you are completely new to eBay and your account does not have any feedback, then getting some feedback before starting to sell anything is a good practice.
People are very wary of buying anything online nowadays, so if your account has 0 feedback then no one\’s is going to buy anything from you.
It\’s recommended that you should get at least 10-15 feedbacks before selling anything.
The simplest way to get feedback is to buy 10-15 $0.99 items with free shipping.
Many sellers leave positive feedback to you straightway when you\’ll make payment.
\n\n\n2. Start small - Most of the eBay resellers buy a bulk wholesale stock of any particular product then sell it on eBay at a retail price.
If you don\’t have money to buy a wholesale stock then find out unwanted items present in your house which are in good condition and make a list of them.
\n\n\n3. Research - Now as you have a list of few ready to sell items you must ensure that there is a market for them.
Take 10 minutes to Google your item and uncover its true market value on eBay and another bunch of e-commerce sites.
This will help you to sell right items more competitively because you\’ll have the knowledge of your item\’s market and its pricing strategies.
Also, dig out relevant targeted keywords which will help people to find your items via Google search engine.
\n\n\n4. Craft the title - Title is the single most important factor for grabbing the attention of your potential buyer.
Make sure your title is appealing, complete and you\’ve included targeted keywords.
You don\’t have to be a tech wizard for this. Just ask yourself, what would a potential buyer for this item type into the search box?
\n\n\n5. Write item\’s description - Fill out all the fields in your listing, and make sure your textual description is providing all the information that your potential buyer might look for.
Most of the lazy sellers ignore this and fail badly at selling anything on eBay.
\n\n\n6. Upload item\’s pictures - Upload only high-quality pictures. Ensure that item\’s pictures are new, clear (not blurry) and cover the product from all angles.
Also, don\’t restrict yourselves to 2-3 pictures upload at least 6 pictures.
\n\n\n7. Timing - Most of the expert sellers use 10-day listing starting on Thursday, you should use it too, it will give you two full weekends of eyeballs. You\’ll usually receive the highest traffic on weekends.”
        \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\nMonetization is very simple. More people place orders with you more money you make.
\n\n\nYour item quality and delivery influence your user feedback which directly affects your order placement. So make sure you are delivering items with good quality.
eBay handles all your transactions securely so you don\’t need to worry about any payment processing issues.
Once you are in a profit-making stage, buy your most selling products in bulk at a wholesale price and then sell them on retail price to increase your profits.
Rinse and repeat.

</string>

    <string name="amazon">
        \n\n\n<b><u>What is the Amazon Associates Program?</u></b>
\n\n\nAmazon Associates is an affiliate marketing program that allows website owners and bloggers to create links and earns referral commissions when any of the website visitors clicks through and buys products from Amazon.
\n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. People who love to write, explain things in details and would like to share their knowledge and expertise with the world.
\n\n\n2. Best for people who already own a blog or website with some daily traffic.
\n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Ability to express knowledge in writing with simpler yet effective way.
\n\n\n2. Ability to persuade and convince people through right argument and explanation.
\n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Becoming An Amazon Associate -</u></b>
\n\n\nFirst, you should sign up for the Amazon Associate program. You\’ll need to provide your website\’s name while signing up.
\n\n\nAmazon will analyze your website, and if they find it appropriate according to their standards they will approve you as an official Amazon associate. The approval process might take 2 to 5 days.
 
\n\n\nOnce you\’re approved, find out the relevant products you want to promote on your blog then grab their affiliate links and insert them into your website.
\n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Dig out relevant products - The first and most important thing is to find out the products that are relevant to your website\’s or blog\’s content and audience.
\n\n\nThe more relevant the product, the better chance you\’ll have of selling.
\n\n\nFor example, promoting wristwatches on a blog that teaches people to do Yoga exercises is highly unlikely to make you any sale. But instead, if you try to promote Yoga mats, pants and books you\’ll see great success.
\n\n\n2. Place affiliate links inside your content - Placing simple text links within the context of an article is the most effective way to get people click your affiliate links.
\n\n\nPeople trust the body of the content on a page more than any other area of the website. Hence it is very likely that they will click on the link when it\’s placed inside the content\’s body.
\n\n\n3. Link product images to Amazon - Images play an important role in grabbing visitor\’s attention.
\n\n\nAnother simple way to get people click on your affiliate links is to use lots of high-quality product images and make those images as clickable affiliate links.
\n\n\nOne good thing about Amazon is that it allows you to freely use any product\’s image on your website for promotional purposes.
\n\n\n4. Write a product review article - Doing a quality product review and writing a great article explaining all the facets of a product is another great way to generate high click-through rates and sales.
\n\n\nBut while doing any review make sure it is of high quality and unbiased. People shouldn\’t think that you are badly trying to get them buy the product.
\n\n\nA high-quality review should answer all the answers and clear confusion or reservations any potential buyer might have. Make sure your review does cover all the above-mentioned aspects.
\n\n\n5. Just send people to Amazon - One of the great things about Amazon is that it is very good at converting visitors into buyers.
\n\n\nYou don\’t need to follow them nor target them with ads, Amazon will do the rest for you. All you need to do is send them to Amazon.com through your affiliate link.
\n\n\nThe great thing about this is when somebody visits Amazon.com through your link you get a percentage of anything they buy for the next 24 hours.
\n\n\nFor example,  if one person clicks on your “Yoga Mat” affiliate link and visits Amazon.com and buys 2 wrist watches instead of a Yoga Mat within 24 hours,  you\’ll get commissions for the wrist watch sales even if you didn\’t promote it directly.
\n\n\n6. Build loyalty and trust - One major factor that will boost your sales is your reader\’s\’ loyalty and trust towards you and your website. Most of your sales will come people who are loyal and repeat readers.
\n\n\nReaders who connect with you on a regular basis, over the long period, begin to trust you and your website. So when you make any recommendation or do a review, they are more likely to take that advice than someone who they don\’t trust.
        \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\nMonetization formula is almost similar to most of the other methods discussed in this app. More people visit Amazon.com via your affiliate link and buy products, more money you make.
\n\n\nAmazon.com will handle all the payment and commission processing for you so you don\’t need to worry about it.
</string>
    <string name="cpa">\n\n\n<b><u>What is CPA?</u></b>
\n\n\nCPA stands for “Cost Per Action."
\n\n\nCPA is one of the popular ways of making money on the internet. CPA marketing is very simple: you get paid when someone clicks on your affiliate link and completes an action.
\n\n\nThat action could be:
\n•	Providing an email address
\n•	Signing up for a free trial of a product
\n•	Downloading a mobile app
\n•	Requesting a quote
\n\n\nCPA is easier because you\’ll earn money even if a product is not sold. Unlike affiliate marketing where somebody must purchase a product for you to receive commissions.
\n\n\nCPA model works on lead generation. Many big companies are willing to pay big commissions for generating targeted leads.
\n\n\nYour job is to just get them a lead, they will do rest of the work for generating a sale from those leads.
\n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. People who love to talk, write, explain and have the ability to persuade.
\n\n\n2. Best for people who already own a blog or website with some daily traffic.
\n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Ability to promote CPA affiliate links using social media, videos, forum marketing, paid ads, etc.
\n\n\n2. Ability to persuade and convince people through right argument and explanation.
\n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Starting CPA Marketing -</u></b>
\n\n\nTo start CPA marketing and earn commissions you need find an offer to promote, then get accepted by a CPA network.
\n\n\nYou can find an offer almost instantly but getting accepted into a CPA network might take a week.
\n\n\nBut, once accepted you can instantly start promoting an offer of your wish.
\n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Find different offers - Your first step here will be to find different CPA offers available in the market. And the best way to dig them out is to visit oDigger.com and OfferVault.com.
Both these sites work as search engines for finding CPA offers. They aggregate offers from all the reputed CPA networks available worldwide.
\n\n\n2. Select your perfect offer - If you already own a blog in any particular niche then select an offer related to that niche. Make sure it is relevant to your blog and audience.
For e.g. If your blog talks about android app gaming, then a CPA offer which pays you when somebody installs an android game app would be perfect for you.
\n\n\n3. Getting accepted - Believe or not but getting accepted into CPA networks has become a huge stumbling block for most of the marketers. Most of the CPA networks nowadays implement tough scrutiny to ensure that only high quality and legitimate marketers get access to their offers. This is to prevent any fraud or any illegitimate activity.
\n\n\nFollowing are few tips which will help you to get in:
Be honest - CPA networks filter out scammers and not the legitimate people. So make sure the information you provide is real and isn\’t shady. Don\’t try to trick them.
Know you offer - If you already know what offer you want to promote then it\’s a great plus point. You\’ll be asked about it when you\’ll fill out the application. This shows that you are one with a plan.
Know your traffic sources - While filling out your application you\’ll be asked about your traffic sources. So you must know how people are going to reach your offer. Are you going to promote it through email marketing, mobile ads, writing an article on a blog or anything else, you must clearly mention it.
\n\n\n4. Optimize your blog - Once you\’ve joined a network and selected your CPA offer, it\’s the time to promote it on your blog. The best way to do this to integrate your affiliate links in the blog\’s content.
This is so far the best way to get higher click-through rates. Another way is you can place banners either on in the header or sidebar section.
Always do some experiments and try to optimize your link placement to maximize your click-through rates, but while doing so ensure that you are damaging your blog\’s user experience.
        \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\nCommissions for CPA offers usually range from $0.10 to $10 per action. In some niches such as Insurance, Attorney, Antivirus Software it can go up to $50 per action.
\n\n\nImagine if you could get 10 people to download a trial version of an antivirus software which pays you $50 per install, you\’ll earn $500 without even selling anything.
\n\n\nCommissions offered are decided based on the factors such as niche, back-end product cost, product demand and supply, targeted country and so on.
\n\n\nIn order to earn maximum commissions, it is best that you choose offers which are relevant to your audience and pay higher commissions.
</string>
    <string name="etsy">
      \n\n\n<b><u>What is Etsy.com?</u></b>
\n\n\nEtsy.com is an online buyer and seller community similar to eBay but focuses on selling arts, crafts handmade or vintage items and supplies.
\n\n\nWith around 30 million visitors per month, Etsy provides a wonderful platform for artisans, crafters and creative designers which helps them in spreading their work to the worldwide audience and grow their business.
\n\n\nYour aim should be to leverage Etsy\’s powerful visitor base to reach millions of people and sell your products to them without getting into the hassle of creating your own website, promoting it and handling payment processing.
\n\n\nTop Etsy sellers make up to 1 million dollars a year by selling arts, crafts and handmade items. If you take action, you can also be one among them.
\n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For - </u></b>
\n\n\nArtistic and craftier people who love to envision, design and create their own items/products.
\n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required - </u></b>
\n\n\n1. Creative abilities to imagine, think, design and create items which can be sold online.
\n\n\n2. Ability to promote your Etsy store using social media channels such as Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter. And through blogging, guest posting, networking.
      \n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Creating Your Store On Etsy -</u></b>
\n\n\nYou can register on Etsy almost instantly. But while creating your store you\’ll need to craft its title, get photos of items that you want to sell, write a compelling description, decide on pricing points. To complete the above-mentioned steps it might one or two days.
\n\n\n<b><u>Tips - </u></b>
\n\n\n1. Decide what you are going to sell - Before getting your feet inside Etsy make a list of list of items that you think you can create.
Once the list is ready, go to Etsy and type in keywords to find other sellers who offer similar items which you are planning to sell.
Discover what they are selling? how do their products differ from others? What are their pricing strategies? Do some competition analysis and try to find items on your list which will face less competition.

\n\n\nBased on your initial research and competition analysis finalize an item which you think will be more suitable for creating your initial space on Etsy.
\n\n\n2. Select a name for your store - Once you register an account with Etsy, the first thing you\’ll have to do is to setup your store. And naming your store is the first step of the setup process.
Select a name that represents what you want to sell. But don\’t waste your time on lingering for finding a perfect name.
Etsy gives you one more chance to rename your store, so pick a name right away, and give it more thought later on.
\n\n\n3. Set up your store - Following are the important steps you\’ll need to follow while setting up for the store.
\n\n\n- Create a logo
\n\n\nCreating a logo is very important for building a brand and improving credibility. Make sure the logo you design is unique and represents the items you want to sell. If you don\’t have graphic design skills it\’s always better to outsource the logo designing task to somebody on Fiverr. Tell them what you want and let the Fiverr experts do the job for you.
\n\n\n- Take appealing item photos
\n\n\nPhotos are going to be the first point of contact between your potential customer and your item.
\n\n\nSo you need to make sure that your item photos do the job catching customer\’s eyeballs and convince him/her to read the description.
\n\n\nIf they don\’t find item\’s photos appealing then they\’ll never bother reading your item\’s description. One trick is to study the photographs of other successful stores who sell similar items like yours and then replicate their technique.
\n\n\nIf possible try to take photos using a DSLR and use white plain backgrounds.
\n\n\n- Offer varying price points and sizes
\n\n\nMost of the successful Etsy sellers offer varying item sizes and prices, this helps them to attract all levels of buyers. This strategy helps them to ensure that there is always something for everyone.
\n\n\nFor example, If you sell smaller original pieces at a lower price point, people who cannot afford to buy large expensive pieces can still buy from you. In this way, you\’ll cater the needs of both expensive and budget buyers.
\n\n\n5. Write compelling description - Your item\’s description is the second most important factor after photos, it does the job of persuading potential customers to place an order with you. So make sure that you write the most compelling item description.
\n\n\nThe best way to start is to study what your competitors have written their description, study the biggest questions that your potential customer ask.
\n\n\nTake notes and model your description based on your notes. Also, try to answer potential customer\’s questions so that they don\’t have any reservations while placing an order with you.
\n\n\nAlso communicate important details about your item such as dimensions, the material used, care to be taken during use and so on.
\n\n\n6. Include right tags and keywords - Most of the potential customers will find your store through search. So you need to make sure that your title and description has right keywords incorporated into them.
\n\n\nTo generate a list of keywords, think about what your potential customer would type into the search bar to find what you\’re selling.
\n\n\nSnoop into your competitor\’s title and description to dig out more relevant keywords. Also, make a list of relevant keywords that appear in the auto-suggested list of Etsy\’s search bar and add them to your listings.
\n\n\nOther Options To Etsy -
\n\n\nWhen you are planning to sell arts and crafts item Etsy should be your first choice of platform. But if you want to expand your reach even further you should consider selling your arts on the following websites.
\n\n\nHere\’s the list of the sites optional to Etsy:
\n•	Zibbet.com
\n•	HandmadeArtists.com
\n•	UncommonGoods.com
\n•	AftCra.com
\n•	HyenaCart.com
      \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize - </u></b>
\n\n\nMonetization is very simple. More people place orders with you more money you make.
\n\n\nYour customer\’s rating is going to have a huge impact on improving your sales, brand buildup and credibility. So make sure that you deliver quality items within your promised delivery dates.
\n\n\nTake time and care while packaging your item so that it doesn\’t bend, chip or break in transit. Try to cover the cost of packing materials into your shipping charges.
\n\n\n\n\n\nThat\’s all!
Happy selling arts and crafts on Etsy.
</string>
    <string name="leapforce">
        \n\n\n<b><u>What is Leapforce?</u></b>
\n\nLeapforce is a US-based company that provides work at home opportunities across the globe. They will mostly offer you an online job of “Personalized Search Engine Evaluator.”
\n\nJoining Leapforce is one of the most legitimate ways of making money online from home, and you must definitely think of giving it a shot.
\n\nI am insisting Leapforce because you don\’t have to invest any money nor start any business. It\’s a perfect start for someone who has no money at all.
\n\nLeapforce is an independent company contracted by Google, Bing and other big search engines to help them assess their algorithms. Such companies always hire real people to help them in this process.
\n\nAs a search engine evaluator, your job is to follow the instructions given to you in the assignments, research and analyze the search engine results.
\n\nYou\’ll have to provide feedback on search engine results by measuring the relevance and usefulness of web pages in relation to given predefined queries.
\n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
\n\n\nAnyone who has a laptop and a decent speed internet connection.
\n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. People who have excellent web research skills and analytical abilities.
\n\n\n2. People having good verbal and written communication skills.
\n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Becoming Leapforce Agent -</u></b>
\n\n\nIn order to get hired, you need to visit Leapforce\’s job listing page, fill out an online application and upload your resume. If you are shortlisted you are required to take and pass a three-part qualification exam.
\n\nThe exam will test your theoretical and practical knowledge about web research and search engine evaluation.
\n\nThe qualification exam is challenging and you must take it seriously. If you fail in the first attempt you can still re-appear one more time.
\n\nIt takes mostly 14 days to complete all the processes from registration till final qualification.
\n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Position yourself as an ideal candidate – To improve your chances of acceptance, you must be an active user of Google\’s search engine and Google\’s other popular products such as Gmail, Youtube, Google Play and Google+.
\n\n\n2. Fulfilling other important requirements – To get accepted you must use Google Play at least once per week; use Google+ more than once per month and have more than 11 people in per circle. You must have a Gmail account with web history turn on.
\n\n\n3. Study well – Leapforce will provide you all the study material required for preparing your initial qualification exam. Make sure you study them well before taking an attempt.
\n\n\nRemember you are allowed to take only two attempts, if you fail at both of them then you\’ll never be able to apply to Leapforce in future.
        \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\nYou\’ll earn $13/hour if you\’re a U.S. citizen and $7/hour if you are a citizen of any Asian or African country.
\n\n\nAll the payments are sent at the end of the month by cheques.
</string>
    <string name="wordpress">
        \n\n\n<b><u>What is Wordpress?</u></b>
\n\n\nWordpress is the easiest and the most powerful blogging and website content management system. 
\n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -  </u></b>
\n\n\nCreative web designers and coders.
\n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
\n\n\nAbility to understand the basics of Wordpress theme creation and write HTML and CSS codes.
\n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Creating A Wordpress Theme -</u></b>
\n\n\nCompletely depends on the expertise of the developer.
\n\n\n<b><u>Tips -  </u></b>
\n\n\n1. Research about which Wordpress themes are selling most in the market. Create themes similar to the ones that are already selling and has existing buyer market.
\n\n\n2. If you are targeting a specific market such as Photography, understand the needs of the webmasters in that domain are.
\n\nAre they facing problems with the current themes available in the market?
\n\nDo they have more expectations? Research a lot before creating new theme architecture and designs. 
\n\n\n3. Create the designs that will cater the market demand. 
        \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\nThere are many ways to sell your Wordpress Themes. Mentioning few 
\n\n\n1. If you have developed a collection of Wordpress themes then you can start your own website, promote it and sell the themes on your own. 
\n\n\n2. You can sell your themes on 3 biggest online marketplaces for Wordpress themes.  
\n•	Themeforest.net
\n•	Mojo-themes.com
\n\n\n3. If you choose to sell your themes from the above-mentioned marketplaces then you will have to pay them 50% commission on every sale.
But the advantage is your theme will reach millions of users within few hours and you can start earning money as they purchase your theme.
</string>
    <string name="mobileapp">
          \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b> 
\n\n\nPeople who like mobile apps and mobile technology.
  \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required - </u></b>
  \n\n\nHaving knowledge of Android or iOS coding will give you an advantage but it\’s not necessary. Nowadays there are many online app maker tools available online using which you can create professional level apps without coding.
\n\n\nHere\’s the list of few popular app maker tools:
\n•	Swiftic.com
\n•	Shoutem.com
\n•	Appinstitute.com
\n•	Appypie.com
  \n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Creating A Mobile App -</u></b> 
\n\n\nDepends on the expertise of the app developer and scope of the app.
        \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
\n\n\n1. Upload a free app on Android\’s Play store and Apple\’s App Store. Monetize it with AdMob, Google\’s mobile advertising network. 
\n\n\n2. Upload a paid app, set some initial price for downloading the app. 
\n\n\n3. More people will download your app more money you will make.
\n\n\n4. You can also promote affiliate products through your app and earn extra commissions.
</string>
    <string name="teespring">
    \n\n\n<b><u>What is TeeSpring?</u></b>
    \n\n\nTeespring.com is the best way to design and sell custom apparel online. You design a product and sell it. The sales money pays for the production of your design and we ship it to all of your buyers.
\n\n\n<b><u>    Suitable For -</u></b>
    \n\n\nArtists, designers, painters.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Ability to conceive and create designs.
    \n\n\n2. Ability to convert designs into digital format using tools such as Photoshop.
    \n\n\n3. Ability to promote your designs on social media
   \n\n\n<b><u> Time Required Starting A TeeSpring Campaign -</u></b>
    \n\n\nIf your design is ready you can create a Teespring campaign within minutes.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Select T-shirt color and size. Upload the design.
    \n\n\n2. Start promoting your T-shirt on social media and/or using paid ads.
    \n\n\n3. More T-shirts you sell, more money you earn.

</string>


    <string name="emailmarketing">
        \n\n\n<b><u>What is Email Marketing?</u></b>
    \n\n\nEmail Marketing is another form of affiliate marketing where you use your email list of blog subscribers to promote a certain product.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
    \n\n\nPeople who love to talk, write, explain and have the ability to persuade.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
    \n\n\nAbility to write promotional emails.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Building An Email List -</u></b>
    \n\n\nEmail marketing is very profitable but building an email list takes time. To build an email list, you will give away a free ebook or an email course anything that will help them in exchange for their email list.
    \n\n\nIf you already own a blog you can create an opt-in form and ask your blog readers to subscribe to the weekly newsletter in exchange for their email.
    \n\n\nOn an average, it takes 1 to 3 months to build a profitable size of the email list. But from a long-term perspective, an email list is one of the most profitable and stable ways of passive income
    \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Send promotional emails to your email list which includes your affiliate links to products you are promoting.
    \n\n\n2. The more people on your email list more the chances of the higher number of people clicking your affiliate links and purchasing the product. Thus, you generate more money through affiliate commissions.
</string>


    <string name="fbmarketing">\n\n\n<b><u>What is Facebook Marketing?</u></b>
    \n\n\nFacebook Marketing is another form of affiliate marketing in which marketers promote products on Facebook.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
    \n\n\nPeople who like to use Facebook.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Ability to create appealing facebook posts and images.
    \n\n\n2. Ability to promote your page on Facebook.
    \n\n\n3. Ability to persuade people with proper reasoning.
   \n\n\n<b><u> Time Required For Starting Facebook Marketing -</u></b>
    \n\n\nYou can easily start Facebook marketing by creating promotional posts and create a Facebook page promoting a product. This can be done within minutes.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
   \n\n\n1. Get more people to visit on your Facebook page.
    \n\n\n3. Start promoting any affiliate product relevant to the Facebook page\’s topic.
    \n\n\n3. If possible, use Facebook ads to promote your posts and pages in a wider range of audience.
    \n\n\n3. More people buy products from through affiliate link more money you make.

</string>


    <string name="copywriting">
    \n\n\n<b><u>What is Copywriting?</u></b>
    \n\n\nCopywriting is writing copy for the purpose of advertising or marketing. The copy is meant to persuade someone to buy a product or influence their beliefs.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
    \n\n\nPeople who have the passion for writing.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
    \n\n\nAbility to write a sales copy in order to maximize product sales.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Time Required For Starting Copywriting -</u></b>
    \n\n\nYou will have to learn the concepts and psychology behind successful copywriting which might take time according to your learning speed.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Good copywriters are paid a handsome amount of money for writing a single copy. In the beginning, you might not earn much, but once you will become an expert then no one can stop you from earning hundreds and thousands of dollars just by writing few hundred copies.
    \n\n\n2. You can start by creating a sales copy for the product you are promoting. See the results and try to improve as much as possible.
    \n\n\n3. You can also earn money by freelancing your copywriting skills. Just register on the following websites as a copywriter:
    \n•	Iwriter.com
    \n•	Textbroker.com
    \n•	Writeraccess.com
</string>
    <string name="joinqa">
        \n\n\n<b><u>Join Q&amp;A</u></b>

        \n\n\nSometimes search engines aren\’t simply enough to find the answers to our personalized questions. That\’s where Q&amp;A sites come in.
    \n\n\nWhen someone needs a personalized answer quickly, they mostly turn to popular answer sites to get the help they need.
    \n\n\nIf you are an expert in any particular field then answering people\’s\’ questions on Q&amp;A sites can fetch you a handsome income online.
    \n\n\nOn most of the top Q&amp;A sites, questions are priced from $5 to $25, even more for more complex problems.
    \n\n\nAll you need to do is provide appropriate answers to questions of your choice. If the asker accepts you answer he or she will pay you the agreed amount.
    \n\n\nAnswering on Q&amp;A sites is one of the most easiest ways of making money online by leveraging your existing skills. It\’s even better because you don\’t need any investment to start or learn any new skills.
    \n\n\nFollowing is the list of some reputed Q&amp;A sites you should consider joining:
    \n•	JustAnswer.com
    \n•	Ether.com

    </string>


    <string name="usabilitytesting">
    \n\n\n<b><u> Participate In Usability Testing</u></b>

    \n\n\nUsability testing is the process in which you need to test out apps, websites, software, etc and share your feedback with the developers and help them in finding bugs, problems or improving the user experience.
    \n\n\nWith usability testing, you\’ll mostly need to find whether the website, app or software that you are testing is easy to understand, easy to learn, efficient and error free.
    \n\n\nOne great thing about usability testing is that you don\’t need any special knowledge, equipment or tools to get started.
    \n\n\nYou can use the equipment you have such as your mobile phone or laptop to start the testing.
    \n\n\nLike many other sites, you need to sign up and create an account with the usability testing sites and finish the testing jobs available to you. Most of the sites will pay you in direct cash deposits.
    \n\n\nFollowing is the list of few reputed reward sites you must try:
    \n•	UserTesting.com
    \n•	Enrollapp.com
    \n•	ErliBird.com
    \n•	Userlytics.com
    \n•	StartupLift.com

</string>


    <string name="joinmicro">
    \n\n\n<b><u>Join Micro Job Sites</u></b>
    \n\n\nMicro job sites are the sites that post micro tasks and pay you once you complete these tasks.
    \n\n\nThese micro tasks can include anything like counting the shopping list items, calculating the total bill amount, do commenting on blogs and so on.
    \n\n\nThe only problem with microtasks is that they don\’t pay you much per task.
    \n\n\nIn order to make a substantial income from these sites to support your living or any cause you\’ll have to complete many tasks and as quickly as possible.
    \n\n\nMicro-tasks are suitable for you if you have lots of free time. Most of the people join micro job sites just to earn some side income and make good use of their time.
    \n\n\nFollowing is the list of few reputed short task sites you must try:
    \n•	Amazon mTurk.com
    \n•	ClickWorker.com
    \n•	Microworkers.com

</string>


    <string name="photography">
    \n\n\n<b><u>Do Smartphone Photography</u></b>

    \n\n\nPreviously I have mentioned about clicking photos using your camera and selling them. This way of making money is also related to photography but it\’s it has a twist in it.
    \n\n\nIn this way, instead of taking photographs using your camera you need to take photographs using your smartphone and upload it using the following apps.
    \n\n\nIn this way, you need to install the following apps on your smartphone. You\’ll be given photographic assignments such as taking the pictures of nature around you, fruits you eat, things inside your fridge and so on.
    \n\n\nAll you need to do is complete the given assignments by taking pictures using your smartphones and upload them back.
    \n\n\nAfter completing the assignments if your photographs are selected, you\’ll be paid handsomely.
    \n\n\nBut you need to make sure that the pictures you take look professional in the best possible way.
    \n\n\nHere\’s the list of the apps you should install to sell your smartphone pictures:
    \n•	Foap
    \n•	Clashot
    \n•	SnapWire

</string>


    <string name="domainname">
    \n\n\n<b><u>Buy And Sell Domain Names</u></b>

    \n\n\nA domain name is nothing but a website address that you put on the address bar of your browser (for example, facebook.com, upwork.com).
    \n\n\nYour main task in this way of making money is that you need to find and register the domain names that have the commercial value which can potentially grow in demand in future.
    \n\n\nFor example, pokemongo.com, 99acres.com
    \n\n\nRegistering is very cheap, you can a new domain name on Namecheap.com for just $2. Once you\’ve got the domain name, list the domain for sale on a site like Sedo.com or Flippa.com with the higher price.
    \nWith this technique, you can literally make hundreds, thousands or even million dollars. In 2013 a startup company bought \’housing.com\’ domain name from its current owner for $1 Million.



</string>

    <string name="socialmedia">

        \n\n\n<b><u>Become A Social Media Evaluator</u></b>

    \n\n\nToday social media has become an important part of all our lives. If I am not wrong, you probably might be spending at least 20-30 minutes per day checking your various social media accounts.
    \n\n\nIf so, then why not to utilize this time for making some money online?
    \n\n\nNowadays most companies and brands run social media campaigns for improving user engagement, product marketing and maintaining an online presence.
    \n\n\nHence, to do these things in a better way, they hire social media evaluators.
    \n\n\nEvaluators are nothing but regular social media users like you who help big companies to manage their accounts, study campaign outcomes and gain insight into what works and what doesn\’t.
    \n\n\nIn recent years, demand for such kind of jobs has grown at large. You can too take advantage of this opportunity and get paid for using social media.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
    \n\n\nAnyone who loves social media and is active on it daily.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u>    </b>

    \n\n\n1. Ability to follow instructions, analyze outcomes, work independently and meet time conditions of the project.
    \n\n\n2. Ability to clearly express thoughts and feelings in English, both verbally and in writing.
        \n\n\n<b><u>What You\’ll Need -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. A personal account on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, etc.
    \n\n\n2. Daily use of all social media accounts.
        \n\n\n<b><u>How To Get Started -</u></b>
    \n\n\nThe best option to get started is to apply for the post of a Social Media Evaluator on Appen.com
        \n\n\n<b><u>What is Appen?</u></b>
    \n\n\nAppen.com is a company which serves web-based businesses and brands to make their social media campaign more relevant to their target audience.
    \n\n\nAs a social media evaluator, your job will be to evaluate newsfeed on different social media platforms and provide feedback.
    \n\n\nDepending on the project you\’ve been assigned you may have to work on Instagram, Facebook, Twitter, etc.
    \n\n\nTo get started check out Appen\’s job listing, then select a job and apply for it, you\’ll need to submit an application where you\’ll have to fill in your personal details, education, work experience, qualifications, and provide a resume.
    \n\n\nAfter that, Appen team will review your application to verify if you are the right person for the job.
    \n\n\nOnce accepted you\’ll have to complete a qualification process over a one week period for which you\’ll get all the necessary guidelines and materials from Appen team.
    \n\n\nOnce the qualification process is finished, you\’ll be instantly assigned to projects. You\’ll need to complete the given tasks which will earn you money.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Expected Earnings -</u></b>
    \n\n\nAs an independent social media evaluator at Appen.com, you can usually expect to earn $13.75 per hour. Sometimes payment also varies depending on the position and the country you reside in.
    \n\n\nYou can work from 12 hours to 30 hours per week depending on the work availability. You\’ll receive an email from Appen team when any work pops up.
    \n\n\nAppen pays only via bank transfer (wire transfer) so make sure you have an active bank account in your name.


</string>

    <string name="telephone">

    \n\n\n<b><u>Become A Telephone Mystery Shopper</u></b>

    \n\n\nIf you love to talk on a phone, you can earn some handsome amount of money as a telephone mystery shopper.
    \n\n\nMost of the businesses and retail outlets today constantly try to stay ahead of their competition.
    \n\n\nTo do this, they need to analyze and study what their competitors are doing so that they can create a plan to improvise their products and service offerings.
    That\’s where they need mystery shoppers to do competitor research for them and get them valuable data.
    \n\n\nMost of the market research and survey companies also hire mystery shoppers for collecting data for their studies.
    \n\n\nAs a telephone mystery shopper, your job will be to call businesses, retail outlets, call centers and ask questions or pretend to be a good customer who is interested in their services.
    \n\n\nWhen you\’re done collecting information, you will have to write and submit a report based on what you found by asking questions.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
    \n\n\nAnyone who is comfortable talking on a phone and loves to ask questions.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>

    \n\n\n1. Ability to speak fluently on the phone in the native language and English.
    \n\n\n2. Ability to listen with a strong focus on details.
    \n\n\n3. Ability to clearly write down analysis report in English.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How To Get Started -</u></b>
    \n\n\nThe best way to get started is by applying for the post of telephone mystery shopper on the following websites:
    \n\n\n1. Callcenterqa.org
    \n\n\nSubmit your Callcenterqa application here.
    \n\n\nCallcenterqa pays at a flat rate of $5 per call. And the best thing is that they pay you via PayPal within 48 hours of completing the call. You should consider starting with this company first if you are in need of instant cash.
    \n\n\n2. Arllc.com
    \n\n\nSubmit your Arllc application here.
    \n\n\nArllc payment varies from $3.50 per call to $12 per call depending on the country and location. Payments are made through direct bank deposits.
    \n\n\n3. Intelichek.com
    \n\n\nVisit intellicheck\’s job listing page and apply for the position of Telephone Mystery Shopper.
    \n\n\nIntelichek will pay you $1 per call in the beginning as calls are very short you just need to ask a couple of questions. Some experienced workers have been reported to earn $50 to $100 per day.
    \n\n\nPayments are sent bi-weekly via check until you reach three-star status after that payment is made through direct bank deposit.
    \n\n\n4. Perstrat.com
    \n\n\nSubmit your Perstrat application here.
    \n\n\nPerstrat works in healthcare sector you\’ll have call doctor\’s office or medical stores for gathering information. They\’ll also assign you shops, you\’ll have to visit them in person and submit a detailed report.
    \n\n\nThey usually pay you in between $12 to $17 per call and even more for in-person shop visits. You\’ll receive your payment via check.
    \n\n\n5. Telexpertise.com
    \n\n\nTo apply for telephone mystery shopping position at TeleXpertise, you need to send them an email at jobs@telexpertise.com and Make sure to include your resume and any other relevant qualifications.
    \n\n\nTeleXpertise will usually pay you between $3 to $10 per call.

</string>
    <string name="dropshipping">

    \n\n\n<b><u>What is dropshipping?</u></b>
    \n\n\nDropshipping is a concept related to e-commerce. It\’s a method in which the online store doesn\’t produce or stock the product it sells. Instead, the store first sells the product then purchases it from a third party for a lower price and gets it shipped directly to the customer\’s address.
    \n\n\nDropshipping is an excellent business model because you just need to set up an online store, make sales and earn profits. You don\’t need to worry about stock, inventory, packing, shipping or handling.
    \n\n\nIt\’s a great business model for someone who has very little money to invest because you don\’t have to buy a product unless you\’ve already made a sale and have been paid by the customer.
    \n\n\nSo, basically in this business model, you are using customer\’s money for purchasing a product and making the profit without investing your own money.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
    \n\n\nAnyone who loves e-commerce.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>

    \n\n\n1. Ability to deal with your clients and suppliers in a confident way. You should be able to answer their queries, solve problems and instruct them correctly.
    \n\n\n2. Excellent written and verbal communication skills.
    \n\n\n3. Ability to spot trends, opportunities and adapt quickly.
    \n\n\n4. Analytical skills.
    \n\n\n5. Up to date knowledge of the industry.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How To Get Started -</u></b>
    \n\n\nThe hassle-free way to get started is by signing up on Shopify.com.
    \n\n\n<b><u>What is Shopify.com?</u></b>
    \n\n\nShopify is a website which provides you all the technical things that you\’ll ever need to setup your online store. You\’ll get hosting, domain name, design, themes, payment gateways and almost everything at one place.
    \n\n\nShopify makes online store setup so easy that anyone without much of technical knowledge can do it.
    \n\n\nIt\’s great a great choice if you want to focus and spend more time on your business growing activities rather than technical setup and maintenance.
    \n\n\nShopify is not just like any website generator or CMS like WordPress. It\’s a complete e-commerce platform with more than 70k people using it for selling products online.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Tips -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Decide what you are going to sell - Before you can start setting up your online store on Shopify make a list of things that you want to sell.
    \n\n\nYou can sell anything from wristwatches to t-shirts, necklaces, accessories and so on. If you still can\’t decide what to sell then try to make a list of things you like or which interest you the most, this will give you a heads up.
    \n\n\n2. Do some initial research - Once you have the list, you must conduct some research. Find the answers to the questions such as:

    \n\n\n•	Does the product you are intending to sell have demand in the market?
    \n•	How much price are people willing to pay?
    \n•	Where are people visiting to buy these products?
    \n•	On which social media channel you can find your best potential customers?
    \n•	What is the age group of your potential customers?
    \n•	What are the current trends?
    \n\n\nThe best way to find the answers to above questions is to visit top e-commerce stores such as Amazon.com find which product designs are selling the best, read the customer reviews to get more insight into customers expectations.
    \n\n\nYou can also visit product forums, join social media groups, popular blogs to collect more data about your potential customers.
    \n\n\nThis data will help you to select the right products that will appeal your target audience and thus fetch you more sales and profits.
    \n\n\nFor example, if you plan to sell wristwatches visit Amazon.com and check out best-selling wristwatches note down their price range, observe their designs, read customer reviews and note down important points.
    \n\n\nFind out other similar e-commerce sites like Amazon and repeat the above method. After that move on to watch forums, fashion blogs to collect more data about your potential customers.
    \n\n\n3. Find the suppliers - Once you\’ve finalized the products you want to sell, you can visit sites like Everbuying.net or Alibaba.com to find the suppliers who can provide you the products.
    Shortlist some good suppliers, discuss your marketing plan with them and see if they are the right fit for you and can deliver agreed products within the time limits.

    \n\n\n4. Set your store on Shopify - Once you\’ve completed the first 3 steps it\’s the time to setup your online store.
    Do this, register on Shopify.com, verify your email and start store creation process. Here you\’ll need to choose your custom domain name, theme, product category and finally, add products.
    While adding products you can use the images and description used by your preferred supplier from Everbuying.net or Aliexpress.com.
    \n\n\n5. Pricing strategy - Your pricing strategy is going to define how much money you are going to make. Use the data you collected during the research step to decide your product\’s pricing.
    \n\n\nFor example, if you\’ve decided to sell wristwatches and they cost you $17 per piece on Everbuying, and your research data is suggesting you to sell it for maximum $30, then you can sell it for $27 and make $10 profit on every sale.
    \n\n\n6. Promote your product links - Once you\’ve added products to your Shopify store you can start promoting them wherever you want. Social media is the best place beginning your promotion campaign. You can also offer discount codes to attract more customers to your store.
    \n\n\n7. Orders and shipping - Once anyone places an order use that money to place the order from your supplier on Everbuying or Alibaba and provide him your customer\’s shipping address. Your supplier will himself make the arrangement for packing and shipping. You don\’t need to worry about anything.
    \n\n\nThe more targeted people visit your store and make the purchase, the more money you make.

</string>


    <string name="music">
    \n\n\n<b><u>Listen And Rate Music</u></b>

    \n\n\nIf you love listening to music and can write an opinion based on your review of the music, then this way can be an excellent opportunity for you to make some money.
    \n\n\nThere are companies, advertising agencies and other individual music creators who need people to listen to their music, review it and write an opinion.
    \n\n\nThese opinions help them to check whether their music is the right fit for their project or it might need some improvement.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
    \n\n\nAnyone who loves to listen to music.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Excellent written communication skills.
    \n\n\n2. Ability to formulate and present your opinion in clear and precise manner.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How To Get Started -</u></b>
    \n\n\nSign up on the following legitimate sites as music lovers:
    \n\n\n•	Slicethepie.com
    \n•	Musicxray.com
    \n\n\n<b><u>Expected Earnings -</u></b>
    \n\n\nTo be frank, the payment you get for rating and reviewing music isn\’t that great. You can make few dollars here and there but you can\’t make a living out of it, but it\’s a good way to earn some extra bucks and utilize your free time.


</string>


    <string name="videoediting">\n\n\n<b><u>Video Creation And Editing</u></b>

    \n\n\nVideos are a hot commodity right now, but not everyone knows how to make them, let alone edit them. This is where you could offer a video creation or editing service.
        \n\n\n<b><u>Video Creation Service</u></b>
    \n\n\nUsing free tools found online, you can quickly learn how to combine text, pictures, and audio, and turn those elements into a video for online customers.
    \n\n\nHere\’s a short list of free online tools that you can use to get started:
    \n\n\n•	Audacity for audio files
    \n•	Camstudio for creating videos
    \n•	OpenOffice.org for presentation software similar to PowerPoint
    \n•	Jing for creating screen captures
        \n\n\n<b><u>Video Editing Services</u></b>
    \n\n\nWhether you\’re a beginner or a seasoned professional, you can easily sell your services to edit videos.
    \n\n\nIf you\’re a total newbie at this, you will find hundreds of tutorials online, both written and as videos showing you how to edit a video.
    \n\n\nIt will not take you very long to understand how everything works. It will take you an even shorter amount of time as you get better at this task.
    \n\n\nTo edit videos for clients, these are the components that you will ask your customer to provide to you:
    \n\n\n1. A script. The words that will go on each slide within the video presentation. The goal is 10 words or less for each slide; the simpler the better is what creates an effective message.
    \n\n\n2. A musical loop in an MP3 format. You can purchase musical loops (a short instrumental or musical song) by category and have them shipped to you on CD, or you can download the loops to your computer.

    \n\n\nIf the customer is not providing a musical loop, then you will choose the musical track that will go along with the video presentation.
    \n\n\n3. Sometimes the customer will provide a voiceover, which is an audio file that you will need to add to the video.
    \n\n\nThe audio formats vary depending upon how they were recorded and saved.
    \n\n\nMake sure you understand which files you will be able to work with according to the free software that you downloaded from the Internet.
    \n\n\nIn summary, using free tools that you can find online, you can learn how to create and edit videos for customers.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How To Monetize -</u></b>
    \n\n\nYou can sell these services to individual business owners by approaching them through e-mail or their website contact form.
    \n\n\nYou can advertise your work for hire services in any of the online forums, and you may even offer your services to webmasters as an add-on bonus perk for their customers.
    \n\n\nYou can even start a video creation or editing gig on Fiverr.com or register yourself as a video creator and editor on Upwork.com
    \n\n\nThe video creation and editing market is wide open right now, and serious cash is ready to be made.



</string>


    <string name="viralwebsite">
    \n\n\n<b><u>Create A Viral Website</u></b>

  \n\n\n\n\n<b><u>  What is a viral website?</u></b>
    \n\n\nA website which publishes interesting, informative or surprising content and inspires its readers to share its content with their social media friends is called a viral website.
    \n\n\nIt\’s a kind of a website which gets popular and drives traffic through social media sharing and makes money by publishing ads.
    \n\n\nI am sure you might have come across websites like Buzzfeed.com, Upworthy.com, Viralnova.com or Boredpanda.com these are the world\’s most famous viral websites.
   \n\n\n<b><u> Why starting a viral website is beneficial in current social media scenario?</u></b>
    \n\n\nToday\’s social media users love to share interesting stuff with their friends or tag them. It\’s a growing trend which can make anything go viral without much of advertising or marketing efforts.
    \n\n\nYou can leverage this sharing trend on social media and make money by creating some interesting articles, sharing them on social media, driving people to your website and make money by publishing ads.
    \n\n\nAnother advantage of creating a viral website is that you can instantly drive traffic to your website via social media channels and make money, you don\’t need to rely on Google or SEO techniques and wait for months to see a steady flow of traffic.
    \n\n\n<b><u>Suitable For -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. People who love to read and write about interesting topics
    \n\n\n2. People who love social media
        \n\n\n<b><u>Skills Required -</u></b>
    \n\n\n1. Ability to write interesting and read worthy articles
    \n\n\n2. Ability to dig out exciting and share-worthy topics from the internet
    \n\n\n3. Basic Wordpress website operating skills
    \n\n\n<b><u>Time Required To Get Started -</u></b>
    \n\n\nYou\’ll need time to setup your website, social media fan page, finding topics and writing articles on them. Depending upon your experience time required might vary, but most of you can get your website running and publish your first article within a week\’s time.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How To Get Started -</u></b>
    \n\n\nStep 1 - Setup your Wordpress viral website
    \n\n\nSetting up a Wordpress website is easy, and you don\’t need to learn any technical stuff to do it.
    \n\n\nYou\’ll just need a domain name and a hosting account with a good web host to set up your Wordpress site.
    \n\n\nIf you need a step by step guide for doing this, you can watch Wordpress tutorial videos on YouTube to get started.
    \n\n\nStep 2 - Create a Facebook fan page for you viral website.
    \n\n\nYou can create a Facebook fan page within minutes, but if you still need any help, you can always get help from Google.
    \n\n\nUse professional-looking photos for your page\’s display picture and cover photo and don\’t forget to fill in all the necessary details regarding your website while creating the page.
    \n\n\nI would also suggest you take a look at the Facebook pages of other popular viral websites and take ideas from them to set up your page.
    \n\n\nFollowing is the list of some popular viral websites whose Facebook pages you can use for research purposes.
    \n\n\n•	Buzzfeed.com
    \n•	Vice.com
    \n•	Viralnova.com
    \n•	Littlethings.com
    \n•	Upworthy.com
    \n•	Distractify.com
    \n•	Thoughtcatalog.com
    \n•	Ranker.com
    \n•	Twistedsifter.com
    \n•	Twentytwowords.com
    \n•	Boredbug.com
    \n•	Sickchirpse.com
    \n•	Therichest.com
    \n•	Boredpanda.com
    \n•	Guff.com
    \n•	Cracked.com
    \n•	List25.com
    \n•	Omgfacts.com
    \n•	Cheezburger.com
    \n\n\nStep 3 - Publish viral content on your website and share them on your Facebook page.
    \n\n\nFinding viral content and publishing them on your website is the most challenging task in this business model but fortunately, there\’s a simple solution to this problem.
    \n\n\nJust visit all the popular viral websites that I have mentioned above and find out which of their articles are trending, study their Facebook pages and look for the articles that have got most shares then rewrite and publish your own article on the same topic on your website.
    \n\n\nA word of caution here, never copy any articles from other websites unless you want to get banned from Google or Facebook.
    \n\n\nThe idea here is to dig out the topics that are already popular then rewrite articles on them in your own unique perspective.
    \n\n\nThis strategy saves your time and also helps you write articles on topics which are already popular thus maximizing their chances to get viral.
    \n\n\nStep 4 - Place Adsense ads
    \n\n\nThe best way to make money from your viral site is by placing Adsense ads, they\’re easy to place, and when your site visitors click on your Adsense ads, you\’ll earn money.
    \n\n\nUse a Wordpress plugin called Quick Adsense for placing Adsense ads in the most optimal way that will generate higher clicks.

    \n\n\nStep 5 - Grow your Facebook fan page.
    \n\n\nWhen you\’re just starting out the best way to grow your fan page is by using Facebook ads.
    \n\n\nStart with a daily ad budget of $5 to $10 and promote your page posts. Ads will help your page get traction, followers, and traffic.
    \n\n\nStep 6 - Rinse and Repeat
    \n\n\nYou\’ll have to repeatedly find, rewrite, publish and promote new exciting content if you want to make money in this business.
    \n\n\nThe more you do it more money you\’ll make hence get into the habit of doing all these tasks daily.


</string>


    <string name="chatbots">\n\n\n<b><u>Build Chat Bots</u></b>

  \n\n\n<b><u>  What is a chat bot?</u></b>
    \n\n\nIn simple terms, a chatbot is a software that can communicate with your leads on your behalf but in a humanly manner, allowing you to engage, qualify and develop an intimate connection with your leads, without talking to them personally.
    \n\n\nChat bots communicate with your leads using messaging apps like Facebook Messenger. Like email marketing, they deliver messages, but via messaging apps.
   \n\n\n<b><u> Why are chat bots the future of marketing?</u></b>
    \n\n\nMarketing on messaging apps will be the future as it\’s highly efficient.
    \n\n\nBusinesses who are using messaging apps for marketing have seen over 70% open rates and over 20% link click rates which is significantly higher than any other online marketing medium.
    \n\n\nFollowing are some statistics which indicate that marketing via messaging apps and chat bots is going to be the future.
    \n\n\n- Nowadays people prefer to communicate with each other via messaging apps more than email as they are more convenient to use.
    \n\n\n- Facebook Messenger solely has 1.2 billion monthly active users worldwide.
    \n\n\n- Top 4 messaging apps have more monthly active users than top 4 social networks.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How are some early adopters using chat bots to grow their business?</u></b>
    \n\n\nEarly adopters of chat bots offer a free lead magnet and ask their visitors to subscribe to Facebook Messenger receive it.
    \n\n\nSubscribing on Facebook Messenger can be done with a click and visitors doesn\’t need to enter their email id, it\’s easy and reduces friction thus increasing lead generation.

    \n\n\nBusinesses also use chat bots for retargeting on Facebook, any person who clicks on messenger ad and doesn\’t make a purchase will get a message of 10% discount coupon.
    \n\n\nChat bots are also helping businesses to nurture their leads through a communication sequence leading them to purchase a product.
    \n\n\nYou can see how chat bots are helping businesses from increasing lead generation till closing a sale.
    \n\n\n<b><u>How can you make money from this opportunity?</u></b>
    \n\n\nAs industry will move towards marketing on messaging apps chat bots will play a huge role in communicating with the leads and thus there will be a huge demand for chat bot developers.
    \n\n\nAt this point, you can learn to build chat bots and help businesses to build them for a fee. The good news here is that they can be built within hours and you don\’t have to do any coding.
    \n\n\nCurrently chat bot developers are charging anywhere between $500 to $6000 for building a single chat bot, over this, they also charge a monthly maintenance fee.
    \n\n\nAs this opportunity is new and the trend is just in it\’s beginning phase, I would suggest you get into this and take the advantage of the opportunity before the market gets saturated and other developers eat the biggest pie of the share.
        \n\n\n<b><u> How to get started?</u></b>
    \n\n\nYou can get started by visiting the following website.
    \n\n\nhttps://botacademy.com
    \n\n\nThe above website has all the information you\’ll need to get started and become successful in bot business.
    \n\n\nYou\’ll find everything from building your bots, acquiring clients, pricing strategy and so on. Now go on and make gold out of this opportunity.


</string>


</resources>
